We're Seino!
Super tough! Strong Energy! Positive Exciting Soul from Nagoya! Team Shach! Purple Purple Kakkari Daikoku Izumi and
Muraho series of Uka. Best regards.
So, this is the second installment of our series on deepening your bond through games, by popular demand.
Thank you very much.
We did it again and again last time.
It was already fun, and it was fun playing the meow meow game.
We have prepared another fun game for you this time.
This time's game is the Crashed Ice Game.
I have seen it.
I am here.
It's the actual thing,
You have to break the blocks filled with hexagonal ice cubes on the board in order,
If a penguin on the ice falls, he loses the game.
The rules are very simple,
The rules are very simple, but the game is played by listening to a roulette game,
The game is very simple, but the rules are very simple,
But this time, we decided to focus more on the sense of rhythm,
This time, however, we made a special arrangement.
But this time, I would like to focus on the rhythm of the game, so I would like to go through the blocks in order without using the roulette.
So you can do it from the outside like this,
or you can go through near the penguins.
The penguins will be in the same position as the penguins.
Let's do our best not to drop the penguins under the platform.
Yes, sir.
Yes.
So, let's do it in order,
Do you want to hit first, Riz-chan?
Oh, me first?
Yes, I'll go first.
I'll go first.
Okay, I'll go first. I'll start from the end. Low key. A little bit.
But that's fine.
Oh, wow. Safe. Safe. A little bit from the end. I'll start from the end. From the edge. From the edge. Oh, I'm scared.
Oh, I'm scared. It's like this... the only thing with legs is the front and the back. Oh, that's right. I'm scared of doing it sideways.
Okay, OK. Then where should I do it?
But I'm often scared. I feel like I'm going to be supported. Oh, yes, yes.
It's difficult. I don't know what to do.
but from the edge, you know.
Me this end.
OK.
I'll go here. In front.
Around the feet.
Near the feet. I'm being supported.
Penguin is shaking.
Go, go, go, go.
Penguin is about to fall down!
It's getting a little bit off center.
Hey! I mean, you know...
I don't care if it falls over.
But there's also the possibility of falling down a hole right here.
Wow, hold still for a second.
It's scary early on, isn't it?
Yeah, it's scary early on.
Even if you drop one, there's a chance that the blocks around it
If you drop one, there's a chance that the blocks around it will fall down.
Oh, no!
I'm still getting by with one.
Oh, it's bad if the penguins come here too.
Don't fall down!Don't fall down!
Huh! I'm scared, scared, scared!
I feel like it's coming closer and closer to us.
It's coming closer and closer to the one with all the holes in it.
Oh, my God!
If we do it here, it's going to fall apart, isn't it?
Oh, it's a little scary.
It's scary, isn't it? I'll leave it here.
OK.
Okay, I'll go.
Wow!
I'm going to go now.
Oh, no, I'm almost done.
I think I'm going to drop off a few more.
I don't know what to do.
Ah, I'm tempted to hold on here.
I can still do it.
Oh, no!
Oh, here!
I'll try this one next time.
Oh, I've lost 2 pieces.
I'm quite nervous because as I get more and more junior, there is a possibility that two of them will fall off.
Oh, I think they might fall off.
I have a feeling.
Oh, wow!
I fell so hard!
Isn't this bad?
With just one swing
I got about 6.
Wow!
It's coming pretty well.
It's already quite a lot.
It's so fine! Micro vibrations!
One by one!
Very fine!
Eeeeee!
I didn't hit you guys! I think there was also a girl who said, "I didn't hit you guys!
Poor, poor, poor girl.
I hear there are a few of them everywhere you go.
It's a little scary. Can I go here?
Yes, you can. Because, you know, this area is only supported by her, so if she disappears, it will fall.
Yes, that's right. She's going to fall.
Isn't this place dangerous?
Dangerous!
If you look at the number of blocks, it's on the side, isn't it? Yes, it is.
But there is a possibility that three of them will fall at once. But even if three fall, it's safe.
These are coming in quite a bit. These three. They are whispering too much. It's whispering too much.
They're whispering too much. It's just the way it is. I'm whispering too much.
Wow! I'm whispering too much. Please wait. I'm sorry. I'm sorry I'm late.
This is no good. Probably.
Oh, no! Oh no!
Endure! Endure! Hold on! Hold on! Hold on!
This is the girl...
Oh, that way?
Oh! Wait! This is bad!
Oh, my God! I'm totally screwed!
Is this it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
I tap here, and this one moves, all of it!You tap here, and this one moves.
I'm going to move the one under here.
Here, hold this up.
Aah! Aah!
I'm going to move the one under here.
Here, hold it up a little bit.
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Ehhhh!
Um, I was supporting it! Maybe down there.
I didn't hit it, but it fell down.
Rizu-chan wins!
She won!
That was pretty close!
This takes a lot of nerve.
It is! I'm so nervous!
Hey!
Do it again?